There was something money couldn't buy
（不良）う～っす。
（不良）ち～っす。
（下川）グンナーイ。
Yo!
Good night!
（不良）朝だよ！
It's morning!
（アランドロン）＜姫川竜也。
石矢魔東邦神起の→
Himekawa Tatsuya...
One of Ishiyama's TKKH and the son
of the head of the Himekawa Group,
１人にして
姫川グループの御曹司→
座右の銘は
「金で動かね～もんなんてねえ」＞
he lives by the motto "There ain't nothin'
that can't be controlled by money."
（子分）姫川さん　例の結果です。
Himekawa-san, the thing you asked for.
あ～そう。ご苦労様。
えっへへへ。
Ah, I see.
Good work.
（アランドロン）
＜でも最近　お金で動かない
あいつに苦戦中＞
But lately, he's been in a fierce battle
with one who won't be swayed by money.
あ～うん。そんな感じで２０人ばかり
そろえてくれればいいから。
Ah, yes.
That's the way. Get around
20 people, that should do.
大丈夫　金なら払ってやる。
Don't worry, I'll pay.
（姫川）
あん時はバカ正直に
正面から　ぶち当たっちまったが→
I might have gotten beat by
that bullishly honest dolt,
今回は違うぜ。くくく。
but not this time...
裏で手を回し　弱点を探り出し
準備を整え→
I'll work behind the scenes, find out
your weakness, make careful preparations,
今度こそ完璧に
お前を追い詰めてやる！くくく！
and this time for sure,
box you into a corner!
お前にはない決定的なものを
オレは持っている→
I have something you don't that
decides everything in the end...
そう！金という最大の武器をな！
That's right! The ultimate
weapon called money!
男鹿ぁ！二度とオレに
楯突けないように→
Oga! I'll send you to the pits of hell,
so you can never make a fool of me again!
地獄のどん底に
落としてやるぜ！
School Shop
≪おばちゃ～ん≫
≪２個ちょうだい　２個≫
（ベル坊）ンダ！マ！マ！ダ！
（男鹿）腹減ったのか？ベル坊。
マ！ダ！
Hungry, Baby Beel?
まだか。そっか。
マー！マー！
Not yet(mada), then? I see...
おばちゃ～ん。
（売り子）あいよ～１５０円ね。
Lady!
Right, that'll be 150 yen.
あれ？いつものおばちゃんは？
Huh? Where's the usual lady?
（売り子）あ　ああ～佐藤さん　今日
風邪ひいちゃってね→
Oh... Sato-san's caught a cold today.
あたしが代わりなんだよ。
I'm her replacement.
はあ…。
ンダッ！マーダ！
あ？減ってんのか？
ダー！
So you are hungry?
しょうがね～な。
Sheesh, fine then...
（古市）おばちゃんが風邪？
マ！マ！ダ！
The shop lady's sick?
あのおばちゃんを倒すなんて
つえ～な風邪。
A cold that can take her
out's somethin' serious.
お前は風邪ひかねえよな。
Lucky you. "Stupid people never catch colds."
（古市）バ　バカじゃね～よ！
知将だよ。コノヤロー！
I'm not stupid! I'm the
Strategist, remember?!
（姫川）
《くくく…購買部は裏から
おさえさせてもらったぜ。→
I've worked my magic behind the
scenes at the school shop...
おばちゃんには　しばらく
おとなしく　しといてもらった。→
I needed the lady to stay
quiet for a little while.
さあ　罠に食いつけ　男鹿。
そのパンには口に出せない→
Now bite into my trap, Oga!
There's all kinds of stuff you ain't
never supposed to eat in that sandwich!
あれや　これやが
たっぷりと入れてある。→
さしもの男鹿も腹の中から
攻められちゃ→
I don't care what you are, Oga,
ain't no one that can withstand an
attack from inside your stomach!
ひとたまりもねえだろう》
あ～。
《くくく》
（ヒルダ）おい。坊っちゃまのお昼を
忘れてるぞ。
Hey.
You forgot the master's lunch.
なんだと…！
ダーブ！
What?!
お！わりぃな。
あと貴様の弁当もな。
Oh, my bad.
And your lunch as well, knave.
オレの弁当？
My lunch?
貴様に魔界のものを
食べさせろと言われてな。
I've been told to make you eat
food from the Demon World.
はあ！？
Huh?
ヒルダちゃんと一緒に作った
マカオ風弁当です。
This is a Macao-style lunch I
made together with Hilda-chan.
カッコ　愛妻弁当ね　ウフ　ハート
カッコ閉じる。
(Lunch from your love! Ufu *heart* )
って何がウフだ！マジ
キモいぞ！コノヤロ！
"Ufu" my ass!
This is really creepy, damn her!
男鹿嫁め！よけいなこと
しやがって！
What?!
Damn you, Oga's wife!
Man, I'm jealous! A lunch
made special by Hilda-san!
あ～う～！
食うか？
You want it?
え！？いいの～！？
ヒルダさん　いいのぉ？
What? Seriously?
Hilda-san, can I?
別にかまわんが…。ウザ市…。
Suit yourself, Annoichi.
はぁ～。
オレもパン買っちまったしな。
Sure. I already bought a sandwich.
ほい。ウザ市。
あざ～っす！！
Here you go, Annoichi.
Don't mind if I do!
《ウザ市　グッジョブ！》
Good job, Annoichi!
ああ…これがヒルダさんの
手作り弁当。
This is Hilda-san's handmade lunch!
いや！愛妻弁当！
It's a lunch of love!
((いってくるよ。僕のかわいい
奥さんヒルダ))
I depart now, my cute wife, Hilda.
((それとアクババＪｒ))
So long too, Akbaba Jr.
((あん待って～！))
（アクババＪｒ）((ピヨ))
W-Wait!
((古市さん　これお弁当！))
Furuichi-san, here's your lunch!
((もうヒルダ　貴之ちゃんと
呼べと言っただろ。こいつぅ))
Now now, Hilda... I've told you to
call me Takayuki-chan, remember?
You silly thing.
((てへ！貴之ちゃんの大好きな
卵焼き入れておいたからね！))
I put in your favorite
fried egg, Takayuki-chan!
((ピー))
((ほう…それは楽しみだな))
Well, I'll look forward to it.
（ヒルダ・古市）((アッハハハ))
((ピヨピヨ～))
（古市）
かわいいね　ヒルダ　愛してるよ。
You're so cute, Hilda...
I love you... *smooch*
古市　悪魔がドン引きしてるぞ。
キ　キモ男。
Furuichi, you're makin' a Demon quiver...
Y-You disgust me.
うっ男鹿！オレの心の声が
聞こえたのか！？
O-Oga... You can hear what I'm thinking?!
声に出してたからな。
だ…まあ　とにかく→
Sure, since you said it all out loud.
Anyway, thanks for the food!
いただきま～す！
んぐんぐんぐ！
おお！ぐわぁぁ！
わあ！わあ！
やっぱりか…。
I figured.
今日は何入れたんだ？
What'd you put in there today?
（古市）うわ～！
魔界スベスベマンジュウヒルの
唐揚（からあ）げと→
Fried pieces of silky Demon manjuuheel,
魔界ウツボ茸の煮びたし→
stewed Demon eel-mushroom,
魔界黒後家ネギ入り卵焼きだ。
and Demon black widow
omelet with green onions.
お前　アレか？
オレを殺したいのか？
Are you trying to kill me or something?
あ　あああ　あ。
さあ　坊っちゃま。
ダブ！
Here, master...
ったく。
Man...
あむ。
あ！
あ～食った食った！
Okay, all filled up!
古市く～ん　魔界のお味は
どうですか？
How's the taste of the
Demon World, Furuichi-kun?
《なんだ！？どうして
苦しまない！》
Why? Why isn't he suffering?
お　お前…こんなもの
食ってたのか。
You actually ate this stuff?
おかげで胃腸が丈夫になったぜ！
And thanks to it, my stomach's
stronger than ever!
《おかしいだろ！お前の胃袋！》
That stomach of yours ain't normal, man!
《まあいい。次の作戦だ》
Whatever... On to the next plan.
ん？
うっ！
※○△…。
Himekawa...
（おばちゃん）
あんたら何してくれてんの！？
What the hell have you done?
う…うええ。
うう！あ～！
（子供）見て見て～！
（子供）これ　どこで買ったの？
Ishiyama Market Street.
What's this?
なんだ？着ぐるみの
動物さん達があんなに。
There's a ton of costumed
animal characters...
（クマ）本当に出るんだろうな。
ボーナス。
He'll actually pay us that bonus, right?
（ウサギ）おう　男鹿のガキを
つかまえたヤツには→
That's right! Whoever catches Oga's
brat gets their pay plus a bonus!
バイト代プラス
ボーナスを出すとよ！
（カッパ）
命かけてもつかまえるぜ！
I'll catch him, even if it costs me my life!
ウサギさ～ん！
クマさ～ん！
Mr. Rabbit!
Mr. Bear!
カッパさ～ん！
（ウサギ・クマ・カッパ）ああ？
Mr. Kappa!
（子供たち）あ？
（ウサギ・クマ・カッパ）しっ！
Shoo!
ブー。
だよな。
Seriously.
ホント　かわいくない赤ん坊だな。
アダア！
You're so not a cute baby.
ややや　やんのか！コラ！
You wanna go, buddy?
（人々）おお～！
（人々）お～。
ダ…。
♪～　今日のごはんは何かな～
ごはん君だ！
はあ？
It's Gohan-kun!
ダーブ！！ダブダーブ！
お前！知らないはずは
ないだろう？ほら！あれあれ！
You know who that is!
You know... that!
アウ？
Eat Rice!
（古市）お前も読んでる世界に
名だたる少年漫画にて→
The world-renown shounen
manga even you read...
連載５０周年を迎えた
不朽の名作！→
The immortal, legendary work that's
passed its 50th anniversary!
アニメは常時　視聴率２０％を
超えるという日本の宝「ごはん君」。
With an anime that gets TV ratings higher than
20%... Truly Japan's national treasure, Gohan-kun!
世界でも一体しか
作られていないという→
Said to be nothing else like it
ever created in the entire world...
そのごはん君の着ぐるみが　なぜ
こんな石矢魔商店街なんかに！？
Why would a costumed character of Gohan-kun
be here in Ishiyama Market Street?!
《男鹿…オレの狙いは　お前の→
Oga... My target is that
baby stuck to your back.
背中に貼り付いている
その赤ん坊だ。→
赤ん坊さえ人質に
取っちまえば→
If I could take that baby hostage,
even you wouldn't be able to act!
さすがのお前も手出しは
できねぇだろうからなぁ》
《くくく　このさい　卑怯だ　何だと
いってられねえ。→
I don't care if you call this underhanded...
使える手は使わせてもらうぜ》
I'll use whatever methods I can!
ダーブー！
アダ！アダ！
《そうだ食いつけ！》
That's right! Take the bait!
《赤ん坊が着ぐるみに気を
取られた隙に…ヒヒヒ！》
While the baby is distracted
by the character...
ダーブ！ダーブ！ギャー！
ペン　ペン　どこだっけ？
A pen, a pen! Where'd I put it?
♪～　おなかがすいた　ペコペコだ
♪～
アウ。
ンガ！
ごはん君のヤロー！
先に見つけやがった！
That damn Gohan-kun...
He found them first!
テメ！ごはん！待てコノヤロー！
Hold it, Gohan! Wait
right there, you bastard!
ああ！こっち来た。ごはん君！
サイン！サイーン！
This way, Gohan-kun! Your autograph, please!
オガ～。
マー。
Oga...
ぶっとびアッパー！
Explosive Uppercut!
うわっはっは～！
ぐあ～！
アー！
ちょっ…え？
Oga! What the hell have you done?!
男鹿～！何やってんだ
てめえ～！
にせもんだ　ありゃあ。
はあ？
He was a fake.
箸の上んとこ。
The real one's chopsticks
are red on the ends.
本物は赤なのに黄色かった。
But his were yellow.
ダッ！
あ…ああ。
（着ぐるみ達）ああ…。
ったく。容赦ねえ。
Man, he don't spare anyone.
《くそ！詰めが甘かったか　ん？》
Damn, I underestimated him.
金　返せ。
金だ　ホラ。
フッ…まだ次の作戦がある。
I still have more plans...
おばちゃ～ん
ゲンコツコロッケ２個ね。
Two fist croquette, please.
（古市）あ～オレ１個。
I'll have one.
（肉屋のおばちゃん）
あいよ。ほら揚げたてだよ。
Sure thing.
Here you go, fresh out of the fryer.
どわぁ！アチ！アチチチ！
Hot!
フーッフーッ。フーッフーッ。
今　冷ましてっから
もう少し待ってな。
We'll wait for them to
cool, so hold on a sec.
ダーブッ！
（お姉さん）ね～え　そこの坊や。
Hey, young lad.
ああ！ハッ…。
あの赤ちゃん
とってもかわいいんだけど→
That baby is so cute...
少しだけ抱っこさせて
下さらない？
May I hold him for a moment?
そうしたら次は　ぼうやのことも
抱っこしてあ・げ・る。
If you let me, then next, I'll hold
you, my strapping young man...
だだだだ抱っこ！ですか～！？
Y-Y-Y-You'll hold me?!
《くくく…前の２つの作戦は
失敗したが今回は鉄板だぜ》
The previous two plans failed,
but this one's foolproof!
《男鹿の嫁以上の
ダイナマイトバディ→
A dynamite body even better than Oga's
wife, overflowing with maternal instinct!
そしてあふれ出る母性→
A baby can't help but
be completely entranced!
赤ん坊なら食いつかずには
いられまい…！》
うふふ。
ああ！
は…あ…あ。
う…うう。
う…お姉さん！
Ma'am!
（アランドロン）古市殿？
Furuichi-dono!
あ～！
Even though you have me, you would obsess
over such an odd creature as this?!
私というものがありながら
このような　何だか→
良く分からない生き物に
うつつを抜かすとは→
さめざめ…。
あ～やめて　もうホントに→
Stop, please!
For god's sake please stop showing
up out of the blue like that!
そうやって　いきなり出て来るの
やめて！
And hey, that's rude calling
her an odd creature!
ていうか　良く分からない
生き物って→
お姉さんに失礼だろ！
じゃあ　コレを。
コレを見なさいよ！→
Then look at this!
It's a delinquent dressed up like a lady!
女装をした不良でございますよ！
じょ…。
（姫川）ばれちまっちゃ～
しょうがねえ。
Too bad we were found out.
I guess we'll just crush
everyone at once then!
こうなったら皆まとめて
叩きのめしてやる！
Since it has come to this, Furuichi-dono,
enter my body once again!
かくなる上は　古市殿
もう一度　我が身に。
え？
Comeback Salmon!
カムバックサーモン！
うわ～！
What the...
なに～！
（一同）うわ～！
Transfer.
転送！はい　はい→
はい　はい　はい…。→
うお～！
We should be able to eat 'em soon.
もうすぐ食えっからな。
ダ！
あ！
ア？
しょうがねえ…おばちゃん　ゴメン
コロッケ→
Ah, well.
Hey, lady! Give us two that
aren't just out of the fryer!
揚げたてじゃないのくれ！
（姫川）あ…。
（一同）ああ…。
ん…ええ。
Why me, too?!
何でオレまで。
さ　家に帰りますぞ　古市殿。→
Now, let us return home, Furuichi-dono!
Transfer!
転送！
（猛獣の声）
おいおいおい　どういう事だよ
これ…。
Whoa, there... What the hell is this...
Remaining Balance: 0 yen
I'm out of money.
（姫川）金がねえ…。
オレ　史上最悪に金がねえ。
さすがに→
I've never been out of money my entire life.
Maybe I did use a little too much...
ちょっと使い過ぎたか。
Allowance: 10,000,000 yen.
Information Gathering: 10,000 yen.
（アランドロン）＜情報代　今回
雇ったエキストラ代→
The fees for the extras
this episode: 300,000 yen.
Store Lady double: 30,000 yen.
おばちゃんダミー
着ぐるみ制作代　及び→
Costume Character Setup: 4,200,000 yen.
Plus the pay for the performers
inside: 250,000 yen.
ナカのヒトへの支払い
お姉さんに見せかけた→
The pay for the guy dressed
up as a girl: 30,000 yen.
お兄さん代
孤島からの脱出代→
Cost of escape from deserted
island: 5,000,000 yen.
Plus miscellaneous expenses: 180,000 yen.
及び雑費…＞
Remaining Allowance: 0 yen
Until I get my allowance next month I'm
gonna have to get by with no money!
来月のお小遣い日まで
残高０円生活かよ。→
これも全部
男鹿の野郎のせい…。→
This is all that damn Oga's fault...
Screw him! I'll never forgive this!
ちくしょう
アイツだけは許さねえ。
お　ちょうど良い所に来た。
お前　行って男鹿の…。
Perfect timing.
You, go to Oga and...
Sorry about this, Himekawa-san,
but can you pay up front?
申し訳ないんスけど　姫川さん
前払いで　お願い出来ますか？
What did you say?!
（姫川）んだと！？
いや…オレも色々
考えたんスけど→
Well, I've been thinking a lot, see...
I really need to think more about
compliance and risk management issues.
今ってコンプライアンスから
リスクマネジメントの時代でしょ。
危ない橋を渡るんだから
リスクの顕在化に備えて→
This is a dangerous bridge to cross, so
considering the actuality of risk, a PDC cycle would...
ＰＤＣサイクルを…。
（姫川）分かんねえよ！
I don't know what you're talking about!
く…てめえなんぞ
こっちから願い下げだ。
Well, not like I was planning
on hiring you anyway!
Crap...
くそ…お。おい　お前！
あ　姫川さん。
Hey, you!
Oh, Himekawa-san...
You, there! Go to Oga and...
ちょっと行って男鹿の…。
それどころじゃないっスよ。
Hell, no, man.
I'm so scared of the old lady at the
shop that I can't buy from her anymore!
オレ　もう購買部の
おばちゃん怖くて→
パン買いに行けないんスけど。
卒業までの飯→
What am I supposed to do for
lunch until I graduate now?
どうすりゃいいんスか。
うっせ～な→
You're annoying. Why don't
you just order delivery?
出前でも　とりゃいいだろ。
だったら出前代→
Sure thing. Right after
you hand me cash for it.
補填して下さいね。
ちっ　どいつもこいつも。
Sheesh, they're all such...
Hey, Hime-chan.
（夏目）あれ？姫ちゃん。
ん？
Whatcha doin' here?
何してんの？こんな所で。
（城山）１人とは珍しいな。
It's rare to see you alone.
Oh, shut up.
うるせ～。よお　お前らは何で
あんな神崎みたいな→
So, why do you guys follow
an idiot like Kanzaki?
バカに下についてんだ。
It's a long story.
長くなる。ここでは言いたくない。
だがオレは→
This isn't the place to tell you.
I've decided to stick with
him, no matter what happens...
何があっても　あの人に
ついて行くと決めた。
…お　お前は
どうなんだよ　夏目。
What about you, Natsume?
A guy like you doesn't have to
follow someone like Kanzaki...
別に神崎の下に
いなくったって　お前なら。
あ～オレは
面白そうだからかな。
For me, it's because I find it amusing.
I want to be wherever is
most interesting to me.
１番　面白そうな所に
いたいじゃん？神崎君→
Kanzaki-kun is really active, so it's fun.
良く動くからさ～楽しいんだよ。
ふ～ん。
Some extra activity, and you'll
be more fun too, Hime-chan.
姫ちゃんも　たっくさん動いたら
きっと楽しいよ。
If there is ever a time you feel you've lost
your way, you must ask your heart once more...
もし　自らの進むべき道を
見失った時は→
己の心に　もう一度
問うてみれば…。
さ　城ちゃん→
Now, Shiro-chan, we need
to go buy that yogurty.
早くヨーグルッチ
買いに行かないと。
こうなったら　オレ１人でも
男鹿ぶっつぶしてやるか。
So, should I just go crush Oga myself, then?
（おばちゃん）いらっしゃい。はい
どうぞ　どうぞ。
But, I don't have any money.
（姫川）とはいえ　金がねえからな。
とりあえず…→
So for now...
I'll throw everything I got left at
him! Even Oga wouldn't be able to...
残り全部ぶちこんでやりゃあ
さしもの男鹿も　フフフ…。
（おばちゃん）フ…それ！
あ～。
フ。
…男鹿の野郎　胃袋もバカみてえに
強いんだっけな。
Well, Oga's stomach is bearishly
strong, after all...
I think I'll quit while I'm ahead.
やめた　やめた。
Didn't you see? I was in big trouble!
（古市）お前　見てなかったのかよ。
大変だったんだからな…。
Here they come...
来やがった。
（古市）
おっさんが現れて　で
お姉さんが　実は女装した…。
Okay. If it hadn't been for them
noticing this small difference...
よし　この小さな違いにさえ
気付かなければ→
This time, I'll get that baby!
今度こそ　あの赤ん坊を。フフフ…。
ん？
ダ。
（古市）わ！
シャキ～ン！
ぶっとびアッパー！
Explosive Uppercut!
うお～！
うわ～！
Hey, two cooled fist croquette, please.
おばちゃん　ゲンコツコロッケ
冷めたの２個ね。
I'll take one.
（古市）あ　オレ１個。
You two come every day. Thanks a bunch.
あんた達　よくも　まあ毎日毎日
来るわね。→
Here. These are cooled down.
はい　冷めたてのやつだよ。
T-This time...
こ　今度こそ…。
I still got this left!
まだ　こいつが残ってる。ん？
（スッポン高の生徒）
ひ　ひゃひゃ…。男鹿の野郎
ぶっ飛ばしてやる。
That damn Oga... We're gonna bust him up good!
Don't feel you gotta hold
back! We're all his victims!
かまうこた～ねえ　皆まとめて
こいつの餌食だ。
ちっ。
Who the hell are you?!
なんだ　てめえ！
おい　こら。
Hey, you. What the hell do you think
you're trying to do on Ishiyama's turf?
おめえら　石矢魔のシマで　何
好き勝手やろうとしてやがる。
H-Himekawa!
ひ　姫川。
やべえ。
Crap...
What? You alone?
（スッポン高の生徒）
なんだ　てめえ　１人かよ。
Where's the posse you
always have with you, huh?
いつも引き連れてる　お仲間は
どうしたよ　え？
They run away, eh?
さては逃げられちまったか
アハハハ…。
Your pals all ditched you, huh?
てめえ　仲間に捨てられたのかよ。
なっさけね～な～　おい。
What a loser!
How 'bout you join our team, Himekawa-san?
オレらのチーム　入れてやろ～か
え？姫川さんよ。
Well, he can't do nothin' by himself.
まあ１人じゃ　何にも
出来ねえだろうけどな。
確かにそうだな…でも
金の力だけで→
That might be true.
But I'm not a member of the TKKH
just from the power of money alone.
東邦神姫の看板しょってる訳じゃ
ねえんだ。
ん。
ぐあ！
Why, you...
この！
うわ！
（姫川）ぐ…。
（姫川）ぐ…！
う…。
Take that!
ざまあねえな。
よけいな事に首つっこまなきゃ→
This is what you get for buttin'
your head in where it don't belong!
痛い目みずに済んだのによ！
フフフ…。
（一同）ん？
Die, all of you!
まとめて逝けや！
フン。
（一同）うわ～！
Damn him...
（スッポン高の生徒）ちくしょ…てめえ。
You bastard...
ん？
This bazooka was for our
anti-Oga plan, but too bad...
（スッポン高の生徒）
男鹿対策のバズーカだが
仕方ねえ。
ちぇ　こういうのは男鹿の仕事で→
This is Oga's job... It
ain't my style, damn it!
オレのキャラじゃ
ね～んだけどよ！
ア。
何だ？
What was that?
Yo. You awake?
（神崎）よお　気がついたか？
…飲むか？
Have a drink?
I don't feel like drinkin' your backwash.
てめえの飲み残しなんぞ
いらねえよ。
（ぐ～）
あ…。
自販機が壊れてて
２個　出てきたんだよ。
The vending machine broke, so two came out.
I was just gonna throw it out anyway.
飲めね～から捨てるとこだ。
ち　これだから育ちの悪い奴は…。
This is why you weren't raised right...
Don't waste food, you!
食べ物を粗末にすんなよ　こら。
Oh, yeah?
んだと？てめえは　オレの
ゴミ箱になってりゃいいんだよ。
I think you'd make me a
pretty nice trash bin.
…うめえな　これ。
だろ？
This ain't bad.
See?
Go buy me some every day.
明日から毎日　買って来い。
調子くれてっと→
How about you apologize for
gettin' a big head, huh?
ゴメンなさいさせるぞ！
どっちがゴメンなさいするか→
Why don't we just find out
who should be apologizin'?
やってみるか　え？
（神崎）んだと！
Oh, yeah?!
あ～ここんとこ珍しく
何もねえな。
Nothing's happened lately, you know?
Well, as long as you can call
picking up a baby Demon Lord,
魔王の赤ん坊　拾って
侍女悪魔に押し掛けられて→
having a demon maidservent show up,
and having a burly transference
demon squat at my house "nothing".
がたいのいい次元転送悪魔が
オレん家に居座っている事を→
何もないと言えるんならな。
ベル坊　最後に　もう１個→
Baby Beel, let's go buy one more croquette.
コロッケ食って帰るか。
ダブ。
（古市）食いしん坊さんか！
You guys are real gluttons!
あ…。
I don't like bein' in anyone's debt.
（姫川）
借りを作りっぱなしってのも
しゃくだからよ→
For you, penniless little fellow,
a one year's supply of yogurty.
貧乏人のてめえにやるわ
ヨーグルッチ１年分。
What the hell is this?!
てめえ…んだよ　こりゃ～！
ん～。
ん？
あ～神崎君　これ全部
賞味期限あと１ヵ月しか→
Kanzaki-kun, all of these have expiration
dates a month from now, so please be careful.
ないみたいだから気をつけてね。
ちょおま。
Why, you...
Natsume, Shiroyama... Do something!
夏目　城山！お前ら何とかしろ。→
Let me outta here!
オレを　こっから出せ～！
Baby Beel's crying so loud
at night, I can't sleep!
Then we'll use a home remedy!
Drink a glass of water
while holding your nose!
That's how to stop hiccups!
On the next Beelzebub: I
won't let you sleep tonight!
Then should I go with the old standby of
counting camel crickets jumping over a fence?!
Camel crickets? Scary!